Thurber, John N., Files /4132
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
John N. Thurber Files
1897-1979
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Thurber, John N.
/4132
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
3108294
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 19, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 01, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6051: John N. Thurber Papers
Thurber, John Newton.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Extension and Public Service Division.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
3108294
- Women's International League of Peace and Freedom, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- American Wage Earner Becomes a in Prosperity, 1938-1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- "Deutschland", 1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Preparing for Labor Arbitration (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Foreign Study Groups, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- International Article, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- The Annals, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Communist-Dominated Unions, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- "IRRA", 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- The National Reporter, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- N.Y.S. Council of Machinists, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Research Bulletins and Reports, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Steel Case 1952 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Union Leadership Training, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Miss. Of Digest Special Articles, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Workers' Education, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Report Cover, 1930 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Condition of the Working-Class in England in 1944, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- The Hutchinson Letters (Box 1, Folder 20)
- History 132 Team Report (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Report Cover June 1932 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- The Druids and Druidism, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- The Movement for the Reform of Poor Relief in England, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- John Newton Thurber, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Report Cover June 1932 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- The Churches and The Air Force Manual Issue, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- The Churches and The Air Force Manual Issue (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Texts of Soviet and Czechoslovak Documents on Forced or Corrective Labour, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Shop Delegates, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  Scope and Contents
  Bounds
- St. Louis Upholsters UIU (1897) (Box 1, Folder 31)
  Bound
- John Newton Thurber, 1948-1950 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- London, 1603-1640 (Box 1, Folder 33)